export const data = [
    {
        question:"Which device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN Cable",
        option4:"Pen Drive",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
        option1:"Asia",
        option2:"Europe",
        option3:"North America",
        option4:"Africa",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"A computer can't BOOT if it does not have the?",
        option1:"Application Software",
        option2:"Internet",
        option3:"Operating System",
        option4:"Mouse",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question:"First Page of Website is termed as?",
        option1:"Index Page",
        option2:"Home Page",
        option3:"Sitemap",
        option4:"Pen Drive",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
        option1:"npx create-react-app",
        option2:"npx create-react-app myReactApp",
        option3:"npm create-react-app",
        option4:"npm create-react-app myReactApp",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        option1:"3000",
        option2:"8080",
        option3:"5000",
        option4:"3030",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        option1:"State & Props",
        option2:"Services & Components",
        option3:"State & Services",
        option4:"State & Component",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
        option1:"SetinitialComponent",
        option2:"renderComponent",
        option3:"render",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        option1:"SetState",
        option2:"Render with arguments",
        option3:"Props",
        option4:"PropTypes",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
        option1:"this.State{}",
        option2:"this.setState",
        option3:"this.setChangeState",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans:2,
    },
];